<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://xin0109.github.io</id>
    <title>Hey friends</title>
    <updated>2021-05-15T08:40:45.679Z</updated>
    <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://xin0109.github.io"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://xin0109.github.io/atom.xml"/>
    <subtitle>&lt;b&gt;My name is &lt;i&gt;XIN NI&lt;/i&gt;, I am the &lt;i&gt;student rep&lt;/i&gt; and &lt;i&gt;social responsibility scholar&lt;/i&gt; at the University of Manchester&lt;/b&gt;</subtitle>
    <logo>https://xin0109.github.io/images/avatar.png</logo>
    <icon>https://xin0109.github.io/favicon.ico</icon>
    <rights>All rights reserved 2021, Hey friends</rights>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple's practice for professional training: ethics and innovation in action]]></title>
        <id>https://xin0109.github.io/post/apples-practice-for-professional-training-ethics-and-innovation-in-action/</id>
        <link href="https://xin0109.github.io/post/apples-practice-for-professional-training-ethics-and-innovation-in-action/">
        </link>
        <updated>2021-05-15T08:32:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This essay aims to discover some of the innovative and ethical management practices in the field, with reference to Apple obviously.</p>
]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This essay aims to discover some of the innovative and ethical management practices in the field, with reference to Apple obviously.</p>
<!-- more -->
<p>This essay is jointly written by Xin, Yujia, Jie, Daikuo, Yiwei</p>
<h2 id="introduction">Introduction:</h2>
<p>Apple has been one of the biggest companies for many years. 42 years later, Apple became the world’s first company to break the market capitalization record of 1 trillion USD, surpassing 2 trillion USD only 2 years later (Kolakowski, 2019). The massive growth Apple experienced was not only due to their sales, however also due to their innovative management practices. One of the practices that sets Apple apart from other companies would be how they have provided free personal development opportunities for assembly-line workers. Therefore, this essay aims to discuss Apple’s practice on equipping lower-skilled workers with essential skills for their career in the future.</p>
<p>Employee training is not anything new. In fact, companies tend to undergo a series of analysis and some already have mature training systems. Training is used primarily for the growth of the company (Business Insight, 2021). However, there are a few commonly recognized issues in the field. According to research, training can be extremely costly, and the chances of employee turnover might increase upon completion of their external training (Brum, 2007). With a higher skill ceiling, employees are able to widen their horizon and explore many other job opportunities available (International Labour Office, 2011), setting the company that invested in them back. With that said, companies would have to carefully decide which employee to train without losing their investments. Therefore, companies may use many strategies. One such would be building psychological connections between the company and the employees, promoting employee retention (Arthur, 1994). With all these risks in mind, companies would only try and send experienced long-termed employees for further training.</p>
<p>On the other spectrum, unlike other companies which focus on training experienced and high-skilled employees. Apple focuses on lower-skilled workers, providing them with development opportunities that they have never had. Especially under the current global trends, where most of the low-skilled work are been operated by automated machines, it is predicted that up to 20 million factory jobs will be replaced by robots by 2030 (Cellan-Jones, 2019). Apple continuously expands their Line Leader program, partnering suppliers and leading vocational schools in China, ensuring their programs are tailored towards maturing management skills that would be necessary towards becoming capable production line supervisors, also known as Line Leaders (Apple, 2020). Apple did not stop there, they continue to improve their programs, introducing more areas of study and new vocational majors until today. Akin to every other company, Apple would also bear the risks of employee retention. According to Maslow, there are several stages in workers’ motivation. From the basic surviving needs to one’s self-actualization (Maslow, 1964). Thus, the following paragraphs aim to explain Apple’s practice in more details, why it is innovative and how it resolves common problems such as motivation and turnover. Lastly, analysing the practice from a critical perspective.</p>
<h2 id="main-body">Main Body:</h2>
<h3 id="21-practice-in-detail">2.1 Practice in Detail:</h3>
<p>As said before, the primary objective of Apple’s practice is to enhance the company’s competitiveness through investing in their workers. Apple has started this practice since 2008. Apple wants to cultivate its workers in every aspect. Apple creates customized education programs to help assembly-line workers living in better lives inside and outside the workplace. Apple also provides basic wellbeing training as a part of its new assembly-line workers’ orientation, with over 840,000 people participating in 2019 alone (Apple, 2020). During this decade, the education programs have become more diverse. Apple started cooperating with other enterprises in the field of professional training to train their employees. At Apple, people are the heart of everything they do and everything they make. In small-sized companies, providing training to such a large number of employees is almost impossible (Fitzgerald, 2021). Apple helps not only managers, but also low-skilled workers who were not able to afford or didn’t have a chance to be educated. The productivity and loyalty fed back from these workers motivate Apple to continue doing such programs in the future (Segal, 2012). According to reports, Apple’s training takes place in-house and year-round. They have full-time academic staff who design and deliver the courses so that employees are able to study the courses tailored to their position and background. The courses are very creative, and they cover a wide range of fields. One of the courses uses Picasso’s drawing “The Bull” to demonstrate how something complex can be broken down into smaller components for better organization (Stringer, 2020).</p>
<p>It is worth mentioning that the conditions for applying are relatively easy to achieve, but the detailed policies of the program differ in different countries and regions. Every Apple staff will enjoy comprehensive training in many aspects, from wellbeing to the awareness of their rights in the workplace. However, in different regions there can be variations. For instance, almost every assembly-line worker in America has the opportunity to be trained, even in the more advanced areas, such as computer science. Whereas in China, Apple has just started to provide limited education opportunities at more basic levels. By completing these courses, workers will have a certificate that is widely admitted (Apple, 2019). From here, we can see that management practices have certainly made societal impacts. Therefore, we must look at Apple’s innovation in a broader context.</p>
<h3 id="22-the-innovative-aspect">2.2 The innovative aspect:</h3>
<p>The core innovation of this practice is that Apple is dedicated to providing free personal development opportunities for lower-skilled, assembly-line workers. Many governments require employers to provide their employees with information, guidance and supervision on health, safety and technology in the workplace (Bluff, 2019). Research has shown that only a small percentage of small and medium enterprises in Australia provide adequate mentoring to all employees, and service and technical training is limited (Bluff, 2019). In most cases, enterprises do not provide general training, so it is even more unlikely for assembly line workers to get training opportunities. At the same time, low-skilled workers also need to bear the learning costs by themselves, because enterprises have a tendency to invest in specific skills, thus ignoring the training of assembly-line workers (Acemoglu &amp; Pischke, 1999). A large enterprise in Germany spends around $10,650 per year on every apprentice for training, but most of its target groups are high skilled apprentices or master’s degree employees. The cost of apprenticeship training for people with University degree and above accounts for 87%, while the proportion of training for people with only high school degrees and below decreases year by year, from 17% in 1955 to 9.4% in 1978 (Harhoff &amp; Kane, 1997). From a social perspective, technology advancement has become a vital part in globalisation, and the nature of human work has changed as populations have grown. Countries and regions have become more interconnected with more developed digitization. Different regional labour markets are competing for highly skilled and specialized workers around the world. Social and economic differences are being created by the pace of change in the workforce's desire for work flexibility and the demand for technology and skills. This leads to higher technical requirements for workers than ever before (Kofler, et al., 2020). In an economic downturn, many companies are unable to provide training for low-skilled workers, besides the decline of working conditions, it is even difficult for low-skilled workers to find a job which creates a bleak prospect for low-skilled workers (Ward et al., 2009). The employment situation of coal miners and shelf workers has shown significant decline in the past 40 years (Manning, 2004). These workers are usually referred as the surplus population (Murray-Li, 2010). However, continuing to train and invest in low-skilled workers is an effective solution, which will not only improve the company's performance, but also its profits in the long run (Philip, 2020). By providing learning opportunities to uneducated workers, thus alleviating the problem of large-scale unemployment in society. When the unemployed workers do not have specific skills, the temporary duration of unemployment will persist for a longer time (Pissarides, 1992). With more advanced skills, the assembly-line workers will be more competitive in the society and they will exert more efforts to improve a firm's performance (Fan &amp; Xiangdong, 2010). In a word, Apple's innovation practices not only provide technical support and personal competitiveness for low-skilled workers, but also bring economic benefits and stronger corporate competitiveness to the company in the long run. It also addresses the employment problem in society, improves the overall quality of workers, and creates its social and economic value, which is also the embodiment of its ethical innovation.</p>
<h3 id="23-critical-analysis-and-recommendations">2.3 Critical analysis and recommendations:</h3>
<p>Every coin has two sides, we must always approach a problem from multiple perspectives. As mentioned before, with appropriate training, the surplus population can be reduced or even eliminated since workers are becoming more educated and employable in modern society. However, it also comes with limitations. Recent studies have shown that lower skilled workers are sometimes more concerned about their wages rather than personal development (Battu &amp; Bender, 2020). Moreover, the relevant costs of designing and setting up comprehensive training systems can be extremely expensive (Taylor, 2018). Thus, companies need to carefully evaluate the internal and external environment to make decisions.<br>
As discussed, Apple’s practice has made enormous influences on workers’ motivation in a positive way, since their desires to improve have been satisfied (Pink, 2009). Wasserman also argued that to motivate employees, it is the best to generate an improved sense of mastery in relation to the specific goal or objective (Wasserman &amp; Wasserman, 2020). At the same time, the process of attaining goals is also vital. Firms can monitor both action processes and outcomes of their employees' development to enhance the learning (Wasserman &amp; Wasserman, 2020). On the other hand, the theory of Personality Systems Interactions states that people are different in social interaction patterns. Sometimes people impose their needs and goals on others (Kuhl, 2000), which might result in disorders of motivation and negative peer effects. A recent study has shown that low-skilled occupations tend to have larger peer effects (Cornelissen, et al., 2017). In this case, some assembly line workers might only be forced to undertake training opportunities because of their peers. Social identity theory suggests that one's self-image is associated with his membership in relevant social groups (Tajfel &amp; Turner, 1979). This implies that such practice can be stressful and demotivating for some. Meanwhile, workers must devote some of their time to study, which can have greater influences in their productivity at work or personal lives. More specifically, the present findings confirm that the principal reasons for poor sleep quality among workers are due to workload and job stress, which might induce tiredness while working and even more serious deterioration in sleep quality (Doi, 2005). More research has shown that depression, fatigue and anxiety are more ubiquitous, appearing in shift workers with less hours of sleep (Courtney, et al., 2010). Moreover, problems generated by inadequate and poor sleep will lead to a notably higher work injury rate among industrial workers (Songkham et al., 2019). Apart from the severe psychological and physical stress they have already faced, extra learning pressure might incur mental illness. Srivastava (2009) claimed that the unsolvable mental pressure could trigger psychiatric disorders in a mass production workplace, which have a strong relationship with absenteeism——a complete loss of labor productivity.<br>
Managers of workers should attach more importance to worker's mental health by establishing a mature monitoring system and recognizing some classic symptoms with great subtlety. Furthermore, managers can regularly examine the psychological conditions of workers through questionnaires (Rao &amp; Ramesh, 2015). At the same time, companies can set up peer support programs so that workers with similar experiences can help each other, it sometimes turns out to be much more effective than other methods concerning mental health (Burke et al., 2018). These supports are essential and should be available at all times to maintain a healthy workforce. Companies must not overlook the mental health issues while implementing trainings.</p>
<h2 id="conclusion">Conclusion:</h2>
<p>Nevertheless, there are other issues that companies need to consider. For instance, the process of implementing new changes in the workplace might create a backlash, as many people naturally resist change (Matteson &amp; Ivancevish, 1987).  At this stage, more questions have been raised, which are out of the scope of this essay. In fact, recommendations made in this essay would only be partially effective and highly dependent on the contexts. Moreover, most companies in the world are not capable to implement such practices, simply because the associated costs are too high. Therefore, to have more innovative and ethical management practices, external supports from governments are also crucial. Despite all the challenges, Apple’s practice still provides a direction of how innovative management practices can contribute to our society in an ethical way. As long as more companies show consistent commitments to implement responsible practices, these issues will eventually be resolved.</p>
<p>Word count: 2124</p>
<ol start="4">
<li>Bibliography<br>
Apple, 2020. Supplier Responsibility. [online] . Available at: <a href="https://www.apple.com/supplier-responsibility/pdf/Apple_SR_2020_Progress_Report.pdf.">https://www.apple.com/supplier-responsibility/pdf/Apple_SR_2020_Progress_Report.pdf.</a> [Accessed 21 April 2021].</li>
</ol>
<p>Apple, 2019. Apple_China_CSR_Report. [online] Apple.com.cn. Available at: <a href="https://www.apple.com.cn/job-creation/Apple_China_CSR_Report_2019.pdf">https://www.apple.com.cn/job-creation/Apple_China_CSR_Report_2019.pdf</a> [Accessed 20 April 2021].</p>
<p>Arthur, J.B., 1994. EFFECTS OF HUMAN RESOURCE SYSTEMS ON MANUFACTURING PERFORMANCE AND TURNOVER. Academy of Management Journal, 37(3), pp.670–687.</p>
<p>Acemoglu, D. and Pischke, J., 1999. The Structure of Wages and Investment in General Training. Journal of Political Economy, 107(3), pp.539-572.</p>
<p>Bluff, E., 2019. How SMEs respond to legal requirements to provide information, training, instruction and supervision to workers about work health and safety matters. Safety Science, [online] 116, pp.45-57. Available at: <a href="https://www-sciencedirect-com.manchester.idm.oclc.org/science/article/pii/">https://www-sciencedirect-com.manchester.idm.oclc.org/science/article/pii/</a> [Accessed 21 April 2021].</p>
<p>Brum, S., 2007. What Impact Does Training Have on Employee Commitment and Employee Turnover?. [online] Digitalcommons.uri.edu. Available at: <a href="https://digitalcommons.uri.edu/cgi/viewcontent.cgi?article=1022&amp;context=lrc_paper_series">https://digitalcommons.uri.edu/cgi/viewcontent.cgi?article=1022&amp;context=lrc_paper_series</a> [Accessed 21 April 2021].</p>
<p>Burke, E., Pyle, M., Machin, K., Varese, F. and Morrison, A., 2019. The effects of peer support on empowerment, self-efficacy, and internalized stigma: A narrative synthesis and meta-analysis. Stigma and Health, 4(3), pp.337-356.</p>
<p>Business Insight, 2021. The Importance of Training and Development in the Workplace. [online] 2020 Project Management. Available at: <a href="https://2020projectmanagement.com/resources/project-management-training-and-qualifications/the-importance-of-training-and-development-in-the-workplace#:~:text=A%20training%20program%20allows%20you,each%20employee%20needs%20to%20improve.&amp;text=Providing%20the%20necessary%20training%20creates,help%20and%20supervision%20from%20others.">https://2020projectmanagement.com/resources/project-management-training-and-qualifications/the-importance-of-training-and-development-in-the-workplace#:~:text=A training program allows you,each employee needs to improve.&amp;text=Providing the necessary training creates,help and supervision from others.</a> [Accessed 19 April 2021].</p>
<p>Cornelissen, T., Dustmann, C. &amp; Schönberg, U., 2017. Peer effects in the workplace. American Economic Review, 107(2), pp. 425-56.</p>
<p>Courtney, J., Francis, A. and Paxton, S., 2010. Caring for the Carers: Fatigue, Sleep, and Mental Health in Australian Paramedic Shiftworkers. The Australian and New Zealand Journal of Organisational Psychology, [online] 3, pp.32-41. Available at: <a href="https://www.cambridge.org/core/journals/australasian-journal-of-organisational-psychology/article/abs/caring-for-the-carers-fatigue-sleep-and-mental-health-in-australian-paramedic-shiftworkers/8756A60B85CAD3BFBF93B63FB1D5703C">https://www.cambridge.org/core/journals/australasian-journal-of-organisational-psychology/article/abs/caring-for-the-carers-fatigue-sleep-and-mental-health-in-australian-paramedic-shiftworkers/8756A60B85CAD3BFBF93B63FB1D5703C</a> [Accessed 21 April 2021].</p>
<p>Cellan-Jones, R., 2019. Robots 'to replace up to 20 million factory jobs' by 2030. [online] BBC News. Available at: <a href="https://www.bbc.com/news/business-48760799">https://www.bbc.com/news/business-48760799</a> [Accessed 22 April 2021].</p>
<p>DOI, Y., 2005. An Epidemiologic Review on Occupational Sleep Research among Japanese Workers. Industrial Health, [online] 43(1), pp.3-10. Available at: <a href="https://www.jstage.jst.go.jp/article/indhealth/43/1/43_1_3/_article/-char/ja/">https://www.jstage.jst.go.jp/article/indhealth/43/1/43_1_3/_article/-char/ja/</a> [Accessed 21 April 2021].</p>
<p>Fan, C. and Wei, X., 2010. Training and worker effort: a signalling perspective. Canadian Journal of Economics/Revue canadienne d'économique, [online] 43(2), pp.604-621. Available at: <a href="https://onlinelibrary-wiley-com.manchester.idm.oclc.org/doi/full/10.1111/j.1540-5982.2010.01585.x#b16">https://onlinelibrary-wiley-com.manchester.idm.oclc.org/doi/full/10.1111/j.1540-5982.2010.01585.x#b16</a> [Accessed 21 April 2021].</p>
<p>Fitzgerald, M., 2021. Pact to assess occupational health &amp; safety conditions, training needs of artisanal miners in Indonesia. [online] Pact. Available at: <a href="https://www.pactworld.org/news/pact-assess-occupational-health-safety-conditions-training-needs-artisanal-miners-indonesia">https://www.pactworld.org/news/pact-assess-occupational-health-safety-conditions-training-needs-artisanal-miners-indonesia</a> [Accessed 20 April 2021].</p>
<p>Harhoff, D. and Kane, T., 1997. Is the German apprenticeship system a panacea for the U.S. labor market?. Journal of Population Economics, [online] 10(2), pp.171-196. Available at: <a href="https://www-jstor-org.manchester.idm.oclc.org/stable/20007537?sid=primo&amp;seq=9#metadata_info_tab_contents">https://www-jstor-org.manchester.idm.oclc.org/stable/20007537?sid=primo&amp;seq=9#metadata_info_tab_contents</a> [Accessed 9 April 2021].<br>
International Labour Office, 2011. A Skilled Workforce for Strong, Sustainable and Balanced Growth: A G20 Training Strategy. [online] www.ilo.org/publns. Available at: <a href="https://www.oecd.org/g20/summits/toronto/G20-Skills-Strategy.pdf">https://www.oecd.org/g20/summits/toronto/G20-Skills-Strategy.pdf</a> [Accessed 21 April 2021].<br>
Kolakowski, M., 2021. At $2.08 Trillion, Apple Is Bigger Than These Things. [online] Investopedia. Available at: <a href="https://www.investopedia.com/news/apple-now-bigger-these-5-things/">https://www.investopedia.com/news/apple-now-bigger-these-5-things/</a> [Accessed 21 April 2021].</p>
<p>Kofler, I., Innerhofer, E., Marcher, A., Gruber, M. and Pechlaner, H., 2020. The Future of High-Skilled Workers. 1st ed. Palgrave Pivot.</p>
<p>Kuhl, J., 2000. Motivational Psychology of Human Development : Developing Motivation and Motivating Development. 1st ed. Amsterdam: North Holland.</p>
<p>Manning, A., 2004. We Can Work It Out: The Impact of Technological Change on the Demand for Low-Skill Workers. Scottish Journal of Political Economy, 51(5), pp.581-608.</p>
<p>Maslow, A., 1954. MOTIVATION AND PERSONALITY. Harper &amp; Row, p.52.</p>
<p>Murray-Li, T., 2013. Jobless growth and relative surplus populations(Respond to this article at http://www.therai.org.uk/at/debate). Anthropology Today, [online] 29(3), pp.1-2. Available at: <a href="https://rai.onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/abs/10.1111/1467-8322.12026">https://rai.onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/abs/10.1111/1467-8322.12026</a> [Accessed 20 April 2021].<br>
Pink, D., 2009. Drive: the surprising truth about what motivates us. 1 ed. New York: Ediburgh:Canongate.<br>
Pissarides, C., 1992. Loss of Skill During Unemployment and the Persistence of Employment Shocks. The Quarterly Journal of Economics, 107(4), pp.1371-1391.<br>
Rao, S. and Ramesh, N., 2015. Depression, anxiety and stress levels in industrial workers: A pilot study in Bangalore, India. Industrial Psychiatry Journal, [online] 23(1), p.23. Available at: <a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC4525427/">https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC4525427/</a> [Accessed 21 April 2021].<br>
Segal, D., 2012. Apple’s Retail Army, Long on Loyalty but Short on Pay (Published 2012). [online] Nytimes.com. Available at: <a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2012/06/24/business/apple-store-workers-loyal-but-short-on-pay.html">https://www.nytimes.com/2012/06/24/business/apple-store-workers-loyal-but-short-on-pay.html</a> [Accessed 20 April 2021].</p>
<p>Songkham, W., Deeluea, J., Suksatit, B. and Chaiard, J., 2019. Sleep quality among industrial workers: related factors and impact. Journal of Health Research, [online] 33(2), pp.119-126. Available at: <a href="https://www.emerald.com/insight/content/doi/10.1108/JHR-08-2018-0072/full/html">https://www.emerald.com/insight/content/doi/10.1108/JHR-08-2018-0072/full/html</a> [Accessed 21 April 2021].</p>
<p>Srivastava, K., 2009. Mental health and industry: Dynamics and perspectives. Industrial Psychiatry Journal, [online] 18(1), p.1. Available at: <a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC3016691/">https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC3016691/</a> [Accessed 21 April 2021].</p>
<p>Stringer, G., 2020. How innovative companies train their employees (Google, Amazon, Uber &amp; more) : HowNow. [online] HowNow. Available at: <a href="https://gethownow.com/blog/how-innovative-companies-train-their-employees-google-amazon-uber-more/">https://gethownow.com/blog/how-innovative-companies-train-their-employees-google-amazon-uber-more/</a> [Accessed 20 April 2021].</p>
<p>Tajfel, H. &amp; Turner, J., 1979. An integrative theory of intergroup conflict. In: M. J. Hatch &amp; M. Schultz, eds. Organizational Identity. Oxford: Oxford University Press, pp. 56-63.</p>
<p>Taylor, T., 2018. The Costs of Training New Employees, Including Hidden Expenses. [online] Spark. Available at: <a href="https://www.adp.com/spark/articles/2018/10/the-costs-of-training-new-employees-including-hidden-expenses.aspx">https://www.adp.com/spark/articles/2018/10/the-costs-of-training-new-employees-including-hidden-expenses.aspx</a> [Accessed 20 April 2021].</p>
<p>Wasserman, T. &amp; Wasserman, L., 2020. How to motivate people . In: Motivation, Effort, and the Neural Network Model. 1st ed. Boca Raton: Institution for Neurocognitive Learning Therapy, pp. 129-143.</p>
<p>Wasserman, T. &amp; Wasserman , L., 2020. Motivation as Goal-Directed behavior: The Effect of Decision-Making. In: Motivation, Effort, and the Neural NEtwork Model. Boca Raton: Institution for Neurocognitive Learning Therapy, pp. 63-75.</p>
<p>Wotschack, P., 2019. When Do Companies Train Low‐Skilled Workers? The Role of Institutional Arrangements at the Company and Sectoral Level. British Journal of Industrial Relations, [online] 58(3), pp.587-616. Available at: <a href="https://onlinelibrary-wiley-com.manchester.idm.oclc.org/doi/pdfdirect/10.1111/bjir.12503">https://onlinelibrary-wiley-com.manchester.idm.oclc.org/doi/pdfdirect/10.1111/bjir.12503</a> [Accessed 21 April 2021].</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[做个人网站这个事...]]></title>
        <id>https://xin0109.github.io/post/zuo-ge-ren-wang-zhan-zhe-ge-shi/</id>
        <link href="https://xin0109.github.io/post/zuo-ge-ren-wang-zhan-zhe-ge-shi/">
        </link>
        <updated>2021-05-15T08:10:51.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>我已经想做网站很久了，从高中学JAVA开始。<br>
但是因为当时实在是没空，19年高中毕业后有空了，但又忘记了。<br>
这回终于把网站搭建起来了，虽然不是我自己写的码吧（github yyds）</p>
<p>这个网站的初衷就是分享和记录。通过论文，博客或者日记的形式记录我的生活，和大家分享我的经历和意见</p>
<p>在这里感谢大家前来捧场！<br>
也希望自己能够持续更新，如果真能坚持下去，之后开始拍视频做VLOG也说不定～</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Equality, Diversity and Inclusion in University]]></title>
        <id>https://xin0109.github.io/post/equality-diversity-and-inclusion-essay/</id>
        <link href="https://xin0109.github.io/post/equality-diversity-and-inclusion-essay/">
        </link>
        <updated>2021-05-15T07:18:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>In this essay, we discuss the current equality issues in universities around the world, such as education to underrepresented groups and gender equality at the workplace.</p>
]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>In this essay, we discuss the current equality issues in universities around the world, such as education to underrepresented groups and gender equality at the workplace.</p>
<!-- more -->
<h2 id="introduction">Introduction</h2>
<p>University plays a key role in the changes and transformations in our society (Brennan, et al., 2004). In recent years, issues regarding equality, diversity and inclusion (EDI) have become the central topic around the world and universities must take initiatives to solve these problems. Equality is often regarded as having equal rights and opportunities instead of everyone being identical (Caruana &amp; Ploner, 2010). Scheffler claims that equality can be classified as distributive and relational equality. The former refers to egalitarian distribution of resources, whereas the latter is an ideal governing certain kind of interpersonal relationships (Scheffler, 2015). On the other hand, inequality and discrimination against certain groups has existed for centuries. Woman’s right to education and racial segregation are historical examples of inequality in education due to differences in gender and race (Zajda, 2009). In recent years, these differences have been reconceptualized as diversity, and it is defined or perceived as a competitive advantage, a diverse group of people are able to bring new skills and aptitudes (Wood, et al., 2006). Diversity can be either physical which refers to bio-demographic differences, or cognitive, differences in perspectives and problem-solving habits (ELI Inc., 2020). Inclusion in the broader sense is to embrace the minorities so that they feel accepted and equally treated (Global Diversity Practice, 2020). However, inclusivity these days often exclusively refers to disability education (Schuelka, et al., 2019).</p>
<p>Bear in mind that these interpretations are not definite. Educators in the fields lack a common understanding of these concepts. One of the examples is the Least Restrictive Environment law in the US, which states that students with disabilities should study alongside with other peers in the same classroom (Copenhaver, 2006). However, Crockett and Kauffman argued that such an approach to inclusion might result in an even more restrictive environment for disabled students than segregated classrooms (Crockett &amp; Kauffman, 2013). These differences in understanding are due to perspectives and personality traits. Students with disabilities who are also outgoing might enjoy studying with other peers, whereas some might find it awkward and depressing (Ashton, 2013). The social identity theory suggests that one’s self image is associated with the comparisons between himself and relevant social groups, which can also have significant impacts on intergroup behaviours (Tajfel &amp; Turner, 1979). In this case, disabled students might have negative associations when comparing themselves to normal students. Therefore, it is essential to focus on developing both behavioural strategies as well as physical implementations, such as policies.</p>
<p>This essay aims to discover the possible implementations that would achieve a higher degree of EDI. It is crucial to approach the problem from different perspectives in order for a comprehensive respond. It is also necessary to discuss to what extent do these recommendations work in the context of higher education.</p>
<h2 id="main-body">Main body</h2>
<p>Equality, diversity and inclusion (EDI) have become the main theme in higher education in recent year. As there is no one universal understanding to EDI, universities around the world have taken different approaches and faced various challenges. A commonly used approach is to set up dedicated teams and sections on the website to acknowledge the importance of EDI. For instance, the University of Manchester (UoM) produces reports on their progress annually, including initiatives, policies and more (University of Manchester, 2020). This is an effective practice that would not only make a clear statement to the public, but also raise awareness in EDI. However, this information can be selective and incomplete. There is a lack of specific data for each course program. According to research, some fields of study are much less diverse. Such as the Science, Technology, Engineering and Mathematics (STEM) fields. Data from American Physical Society has shown that only about 12% of the total students receiving bachelor’s degree and 7% receiving PhD in physics are from underrepresented backgrounds in the US (APS physics, 2018). To resolve the problem, the University of Michigan (UM) initiated the Applied Physics program where they enhance the collaborations between physics department and other departments (Clarke &amp; Kurdak, 2019). It provides underrepresented students with more information and opportunities to explore the world of physics and counters the perception of “few career paths”. This approach was able to increase the percentage of underrepresented students receiving physics PhD to 23%. Also, 29% of physics PhD were awarded to women in UM, whereas only 17% on average in the US. Many underrepresented students in the PhD program are willing to become mentors for incoming students and it is foreseeable that EDI will continue to improve. As a result, it is suggested that universities should first acknowledge all existing or potential issues to a higher degree of specification. In order to gain more accurate insights and find out the internal drivers of underrepresented students, we can approach the problem using learning theories. The theory of constructivism suggests that people construct their knowledge based on their reality and experiences. The construction is also directly associated with learners’ social connections (WGU, 2020). In this case, underrepresented students might have little or no knowledge at all in many subject areas due to their limited personal experiences. For instance, science is one of the most expensive degrees and students from low-income families might just give up on their interests in sciences (Else, 2015). University should provide opportunities for students to get exposed and have hands-on experiences in these areas of study. This can not only be implemented through university staff, other social connections such as peers and industrial partners can be effective as well. ¬¬</p>
<p>Another controversial topic in EDI is gender equality. In particular, gender equality for university staff has been overlooked compared to students. There was a widespread idea that the student equality is a greater priority than staff equality (DEEM &amp; MORLEY, 2006). A study of attitudes to gender equality in the UK and Germany has shown that although there were only very little harassments or unfair practices against female in HE nowadays, 73% of the participants still thought their university is a gendered workplace and 78% thought there were too few women in senior roles (Pritchard, 2010). More recent evidence suggests that in the UK, of all academic staff described as a professor, only 25% are female (HESA, 2018). This implies that male power still dominates in university academics. On the other side of the world, Australian universities have had outstanding progress in gender equality. In 2017 45.4% of academic staff and 32.4% of senior academic staff are female (Larkins, 2017). One of the techniques is that a sample of employees will be selected annually from every organization to report against a set of criteria regarding organizations’ efforts towards gender equality (Australian Legislation, 2000). This act had great effects in monitoring organizations and provided insights on how to improve gender equality in the workplace. The engagement of community leaders is also essential in order to make greater influence and sustain positive changes (Haider, 2012). An action plan initiated by senior women in Australian universities involved setting up multiple development programmes for female academic staff.  More recently, they have built on this plan which emphasizes the recognition of the contributions of women to universities, the importance of mentoring women in middle management as future leaders and the showcase of senior executive women at strategic points throughout the programmes (Winchester &amp; Browning, 2015). The significance of these strategies is clear, universities must provide extra supports and information to close the gender gaps in professional developments (Traning Journal, 2015), so that women have the same career opportunities as men. However, information might not be enough to change behaviors and this is why behavior sciences are vital in this process (Mantashian, 2019). The nudge theory states that our behaviors and decisions are largely affected by positive reinforcement and indirect suggestions in the environment (Thaler &amp; Sunstein, 2008). Google has one of the most elaborate workplace environments. Creative settings such as treadmills or Tinker Toys in the office have improved employees’ wellbeing and productivity (Stewart, 2013). Therefore, the way that university offices and classrooms are set up can have significant impact on people’s behaviors towards gender equality.</p>
<h2 id="conclusion">Conclusion</h2>
<p>UM’s approach to enhance collaboration between departments, initiatives taken by Australian universities to promote female academics have impacted EDI significantly in a positive way. And their methods have commonalities. These evidences have suggested that universities must ensure that everyone has equal access to essential information and opportunities, identify underrepresented groups and extra support should also be made available for these groups. At the same time, the importance of behavioral strategies is as critical as physical policies. Due to the differences in personality and experiences, educators might not need a common definition and different perspectives are actually needed to address injustices (Schuelka, et al., 2019). Despite multiple perspectives have been taken into account, the coverage of this essay is still limited. There are simply much more aspects that educators need to consider, especially when dealing with personality traits. For instance, the cognitive diversity theory studies beyond the common identity diversity such as race and gender (ELI Inc., 2020), it creates more layers of complexity in achieving EDI. This might be an indication that universities will never be able to take consideration of all factors. But is that the goal anyways? At this stage, more questions have been raised which are out of the scope of the essay. In fact, all recommendations made in this essay would only be partially effective. Yet as long as universities show consistent commitments to these issues, EDI will continue to improve and these questions will eventually be resolved, not only in classrooms, but also in society.</p>
<p>Word count: 1511<br>
Mark: 88/100<br>
<a href="https://xinni0109.com/post/edi-in-university-reference">References</a></p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[At this site, we hope to...]]></title>
        <id>https://xin0109.github.io/post/Intro/</id>
        <link href="https://xin0109.github.io/post/Intro/">
        </link>
        <updated>2021-05-14T16:24:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>🤯Share opinions, discuss the burning questions of our era</p>
<p>✒️I will be uploading essays and writing blogs on a regular basis</p>
<p>🥳It is <strong>delightful</strong> to have you on board</p>
]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>🤯Share opinions, discuss the burning questions of our era</p>
<p>✒️I will be uploading essays and writing blogs on a regular basis</p>
<p>🥳It is <strong>delightful</strong> to have you on board</p>
<!-- more -->
]]></content>
    </entry>
</feed>